Point point five.
And what the indication of our pastor first Christmas.
We just had a birthday.
How old are you, Leon?
80s.
Happy birthday, huh?
Happy birthday, Leon.
Go ahead and say it.
I didn't want to see Mary Christmas throw.
But I love saying that.
Thank you.
Mary Christmas.
You don't have to put that in, Brad.
Mary there.
Well, there are eye-tank you
the way you make the season so special.
And we're personally for the fun of saying Mary Christmas.
I thank you that you care about every person in this room.
I ask if they're holiday time.
Of course, it will be a little tedious.
But I pray that they'll relax and just really enjoy it.
Father, I think of people who are in this room
but who work for our city.
And I pray that even tonight,
you will bless them,
and help them in those moments when they're tired.
And just let them know that we care.
Bless these people in front of you to do that.
Make decisions for our country
or for our community or our community.
And I pray that you will take them
in those moments when it's gotten so much critical
and help them just hang on with it.
And then one of the tough decisions can make you work.
Let them know. Let them just be on you.
We trust you.
And we know you will help them.
But thank you for this commitment.
And for the way you bless us.
I pray in yourself.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
and to the Republic,
from which it stands formation under God
and indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
Okay.
Yeah.
There are four public input,
unscathed with personal appearances.
None.
Five.
Five A, claims list.
Most should approve the second.
So go.
Hi.
Jones.
Barnes.
Aye.
Parker.
Five B, minutes from the December 12th,
twenty-twenty-five regular meeting.
This has December 2nd.
But it's December 8th.
December 9th last.
Most should approve the second.
Easter.
Hi.
Jones.
Aye.
Barnes.
Parker.
Aye.
I've seen budget amendment 26-07 to create fiber department
within the MSUA.
Crystal.
So this action establishes the budget for the fiber's mind
that we have a contract that that comes from.
It comes from three different courses.
When we did the MSUA budget, we had a little revenue.
It's not budgeted.
So it's been anywhere.
So that's $173,000 of it.
$74,000 comes from fund budgeted revenue that we're making
extra money off of our accounts.
And then 42,000 of it were moving out of MSUA professional services
over a specific week about budget.
What's total on that crystal?
529.
This is just a starter.
Yeah, this is for the design.
Motion to approve.
One second, then.
Uncle.
Hi.
Jones.
Aye.
Barnes.
Easter.
Hi.
Parker.
Aye.
Thank you, Chris.
Thank you.
So 9-6 says discussion items with another block.
Just a way of formatted.
There was a glitch in the system and I couldn't make any changes
after Friday.
Okay.
So.
Seven.
Another new business.
Eight staff reports.
Three of us are there.
Solid waste and pollution control.
Any questions on that?
Nine.
Trustee, community announcements.
Can trust the manager communications?
Yes, sir.
11, the Germans.
Motion.
Second.
Thank you.
Uncle.
Barnes.
Aye.
Easter.
Jones, aye.
Parker.
Aye.